<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>imforster blog</title>
    <link>https://imforster.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on imforster blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 20:27:54 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://imforster.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Designing Your Life</title>
      <link>https://imforster.github.io/post/designyourlife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 20:27:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imforster.github.io/post/designyourlife/</guid>
      <description>Designing Your Life Notes Be Curious  Curiosity makes everything new  Try Stuff  Bias to action Try and fail fast Learn by doing Prototype  Reframe Problems  Reframe to get unstuck Step back, examine your biases, open up to different perspective  Know it&amp;rsquo;s a Process  Life gets messy Protypes don&amp;rsquo;t workout It is a journey not a destination  Ask for Help  Radical Collaboration It takes a team Use Mentors / team sport  Designers Ask  How do I &amp;hellip; How can I &amp;hellip; How might we improve upon this &amp;hellip;  Examples</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Coding Problems - Interview Problems</title>
      <link>https://imforster.github.io/post/mathcodesnipets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 20:04:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imforster.github.io/post/mathcodesnipets/</guid>
      <description>Some common math coding exercises used as interview programming questions
isPrime An algorigthm to compute a Prime Number which is greater than 1 and only divisbile by one and itself. For example Prime numbers are 1,2,3,5,7,11,13,17..
Problem: Given a number n the function must determine if n is prime and return true/false.
boolean isPrime(int n) { for (int x=2; x*x &amp;lt;=n; x++) { if (n % x == 0) { return false; } } return true; } Time Complexity: Analyzing this code fragment has a time complexity of o(n/2)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The art of the spike</title>
      <link>https://imforster.github.io/post/artofspike/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 19:34:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imforster.github.io/post/artofspike/</guid>
      <description>Art of Spike  Spike is used to finding out the missing element of the user story to complete. Developer has to estimate the spike story during the Sprint planning session.
 Why a Spike The reason to introduce a spike is that further analysis is required to determine the fesability to implement a technical solution is required. Also, when further study is required to determine the associated risk and/or cost benefits of functional solution options</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use Analog to cope with Digital World - BulletJournel</title>
      <link>https://imforster.github.io/post/bulletjournal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 18:18:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imforster.github.io/post/bulletjournal/</guid>
      <description>How to create a Bullet Journal Learn
Start with a new blank notebook Bullet journals range in a wide variety of sizes from mini approximately 3 x 4” to large 8 x 10” (nearly the size of a sheet of paper).
Setup Journal  Inside cover(left): Add name and contact info Inside cover(right): Key    Bullets Signifiers     • Task * Important   - Note !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first hugo post</title>
      <link>https://imforster.github.io/post/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 16:37:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://imforster.github.io/post/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>Here is some same code
public static void main(String[] args) { System.out.println(&amp;#34;Hello World!&amp;#34;); } Resource 10 minute hugo/GitHubPages</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
